worldofsolitaire.com 2019-11-26

# Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [https://worldofsolitaire.com](https://worldofsolitaire.com/). It applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:  

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We partner with Google Analytics to monitor the traffic that visits this website.  
You can learn how Google uses this information by visiting: <https://policies.google.com/?hl=en>  
This information is used to better manage the website. This information is sometimes shared with various partners including our ad parteners.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future. We have never direct e-mailed our users before. We've only replyed to e-mails sent by our users.

Our advertising partners may use cookies to show you interest based and non-interest based advertising. You may opt-out of interest based advertising here: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>

We partner with Freestar to show advertising on this website.  
You can learn about Freestar's data policies and opt-out of interest based advertising here: <https://freestar.io/data-policy/#>

We use Disqus for the commenting system on the blog pages of this website.  
Learn about Disqus' data policies and opt-out here: <https://disqus.com/data-sharing-settings/>

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, we can restore your game options and show you your game statistics from previous visits. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. This information is never shared with anyone else.

Some of our partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Your Access and Control Over Information:**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**If you feel that we are not abiding by our privacy practices, or have any questions or concerns, please contact us immediately.**

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all the updates will be posted on this page. 

  * FEB 06, 2019: Major update to include language as to what data is collected and why, what control users have over said data, how the data is shared and with whome and and included several links to third party data policies and opt out forms.
  * SEP 12, 2018: Privacy page is now HTML and added opt out links for various advertisers
  * AUG 31, 2018: The Facebook like button has been removed.
  * MAY 22, 2018: I now use Freestar as the ad provider now. I also use Google Analytics. I also now set a cookie to help save your options for future visits.
  * JAN 01, 2018: If in the future the entire website is transferred to a new owner, the user database would be included in the transfer as part of the "entire website".
  * FEB 03, 2015: If I receive an official court ordered subpoena for user information, under United States law I will be required to give out the requested user information.
